http://www.banktrade.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
BT Systems, LLC has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the BankTrade Web site is of great importance to us, and our policy is to protect the privacy of its users. Because we gather important information from our visitors and customers, we have established this Privacy Policy so that you will understand both our commitment to your privacy and how you can help us honor that commitment. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy by posting revisions at BankTrade.
Your use of BankTrade.com constitutes acceptance of the provisions of the Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constituted acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit BankTrade.com immediately.
Regarding Personal Information
We collect information about you that could be used to identify or contact you in the following ways:
1 - Voluntarily Provided Information: When you register at the BankTrade.com Web site, you voluntarily provide information about yourself, your business and the company you represent. In the future, we may also collect other information that you voluntarily provide to us through responses to surveys, questionnaires and other promotions.
2 - IP Address: We store the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer when you visit the BankTrade.com Web site. We will only use this information to create demographic summaries of where our users are located and for system administration.
3 - Cookies: We may also collect information about you and your use of the BankTrade.com Web site through the use of Cookies. "Cookies" are small computer files we transfer to your computer's hard drive that allows us to know how often someone visits BankTrade.com and the activities they conduct while using our Web site. This information helps us generate appropriate content specifically designed for our users and also allows us to statically monitor how may people are using the BankTrade.com Web site and for what purpose. Our third party vendors or content providers may also use Cookies when you select their content or service. We cannot control their use of Cookies or how they use the information that they gather. If you do not want information collected through Cookies, there a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. However, Cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features available on BankTrade's application.
Our Disclosure of Your Information
Except as set forth in the Privacy Policy, we will not disclose to anyone unaffiliated with BankTrade any Personally Identifying Information. Any Personally Identifying Information provided to parties affiliated with BankTrade will be treated in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy, unless you are otherwise notified. In the following limited circumstances, we may release Personally Identifying Information to third parties: to comply with applicable legal requirements such as a law, regulation, discovery request, or court order; in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.
The Security of Your Information
We want your Personally Identifying Information to remain as secure as reasonably possible. At BankTrade.com, security is an integral component of our business and we combine industry-standard technical safeguards with an employee code of conduct to help us provide the integrity and privacy of Personally Identifying Information that you provide to us. Only authorized BankTrade employees, agents or independent contractors are permitted to access your Personally Identifying Information. Those employees that violate the Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. Our approach to security is comprehensive. Using globally accepted security standards, we ensure the highest level of data integrity and transmission through the Internet. We address issues of security at every level, and we continually research and reevaluate all aspects of BankTrade security policies and procedures.
MENU
HomeAbout usServicesEventsContact us
SOLUTIONS
BankTradeCTNet
EXTERNAL SITES
TradeSync EmployeesTradeSync Customers
HEADQUARTERS
BT Systems, LLC1940 Commerce Street, Suite 308Yorktown Heights, NY 10598U.S.A.Tel: (201) 716 2666
© 2020 BT Systems, LLC.
Terms of UsePrivacy Policy
